ozee.com 2016-12-23

# OZEE - Watch Free TV Shows, Episodes, Movies, Music, Gossips, Hot HD Videos and Live Cricket Match Online

We value the trust placed in use by you and therefore, we follow the highest standards of privacy guidelines to protect the information shared by you with us.

This Privacy Policy (“ **Privacy Policy** ”) governs the use of personal information shared with or collected by ZDCL from the users of OZEE. This Privacy Policy is subject to change from time to time without any written notice to you. Please review the Privacy Policy from time to time to be updated with the latest changes and modifications.

By browsing, using, downloading or installing OZEE, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms contained herein, please do not download or browse OZEE.

By mere browsing or use of OZEE, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and agree to the use of your personal information in the manner as provided under this Privacy Policy.

All capitalized terms that have not been specifically defined herein shall have the same meaning as provided under the Terms of Use.

This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction and together with the Terms of Use available on www.ozee.com/terms.html.

  1. **Collection and Use of Personal Information**

‘Personal Information’, ‘Information’ and ‘Sensitive Information’ shall have the meaning ascribed to it under the IT Act, 2000 and Information Technology (Reasonable Security Practises and Procedures and Sensitive Personal Data or Information) Rules, 2011.

Generic Information

We collect Your Personal Information/Information when you use OZEE and when You share such information with Us through email or by posting on OZEE or by any other means made available to You by Us. During browsing/using of OZEE by You, We collect information with respect to Your IP Address and zip code. In the event You want to share any feedback or raise a concern, We collect information with respect to Your name, age, mobile number, email address, gender, occupation etc.

We collect information in order to provide you with a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize OZEE to make your experience safer and easier.

We do not solicit any Sensitive Information about You or seek information with respect to Your credit/debit card, net banking or other financial information, except as expressly provided herein. However, if You share such information with Us voluntarily, We will not be liable for any actions, claims, costs, expenses or other liabilities that may arise as a consequence of such any unauthorized use or misuse of such information.

Demographic Information

We may track certain information about you based upon your behaviour on OZEE. We use this information for conducting internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analysed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the website that you just visited (whether this website is on OZEE or not), which website you next visit, your computer browser information.

We may also collect information to track user behaviour and preferences for internal analytics and research. We may also use Your information: (i) to evaluate Your interest for various genres of content, services, offers; (ii) to perform analytics and conduct customer research, to determine Your interest, for identifying Content that generate sales and to analyse traffic patterns.

If you choose to post messages on our message boards, chat rooms or other message areas or leave feedback, We will collect that information You provide to us. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law.

If You send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about Your activities or postings on OZEE, we may store such information.

We identify and use Your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer OZEE. Your IP address is also used to help identify You and to gather broad demographic information.

We will occasionally ask You to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask You for contact information and demographic information (like zip code, age, or  
income level). We use this data to tailor Your experience at OZEE, providing You with content that We think You might be interested in and to display content according to Your preferences.

Cookie

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a web server on a web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. We place both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer's hard drive. The cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information.

You will always have an option not to provide certain information and can choose to opt-out from provision of certain information.

  1. **Disclosure of Personal Information with Third Parties**

We may disclose Personal Information to affiliates and group companies. We may also disclose Your Personal Information with third parties strictly on confidential terms. We may disclose such information to third parties in order to provide You access to OZEE and facilitate or Your participation in any contest, game or activity conducted by ZDCL, to comply with Our legal obligations, to enforce Terms of Use, to facilitate our marketing and advertising activities, or to prevent, detect, mitigate, and investigate fraudulent or illegal activities related to OZEE. 

We will always take Your express consent at the time of sharing your Personal Information with third parties for their marketing and advertising purposes.

In the event of any requirement by court order, government or quasi-government agency to disclose Your Personal Information, We will disclose information as may be legally required. We may also disclose Your Personal Information if we, in the good faith believe that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. 

In the event ZDCL is merged with or acquired by another company or in case of re-organization or re-structuring of business, We and our affiliates will share Your Personal Information, wholly or in part, with another business entity. 

OZEE app contains a software development kit (“SDK”) from a third party, Red Brick Lane Marketing Solutions Private Limited (“RBL”). The SDK is integrated with this app for the purposes of profiling the device on media consumption and other device data and utilizing the same to target relevant content and ads to the device ("Services") pursuant to the terms and conditions of RBL Services ("Terms of Use"). Further details can be obtained at <http://www.zapr.in/privacy/>.

If you do not wish for RBL to identify television, radio and other offline content viewing around your mobile device, please opt out of all RBL Services via the following link: <http://www.zapr.in/privacy/>.

RBL does not collect any personally identifiable information or audio/video/image/contact files from your mobile device. For any questions or clarifications please reach out to: [privacy@zapr.in](mailto:privacy@zapr.in).

RBL also automatically receives and tracks certain data about your mobile device (such as your device-type, installed software and language preference) or desktop interface, your taps and interests; and may create a unique device or user ID for you. In some cases RBL can automatically detect or infer your location using GPS, your IP address, watermarks and/or Bluetooth, but often your operating system will require you to grant RBL permission to access your GPS or Bluetooth settings; please refer to your device’s system settings regarding location services.

  1. **Third Party Sites**

OZEE may provide links to various third party websites that may collect your Personal Information. Use of Your information collected by such third party website will be governed by the privacy policy in such third party website. ZDCL has no control on the operation of such third party websites and You may share information with such third party at Your sole risk. ZDCL shall not be liable to You for any misappropriation of Your Personal Information by such third party.

  1. **Promotional and Marketing Activities  **

We will send communications to You at regular intervals to notify you of, among other things, various offers, new content, exclusive deals etc., that may be available or new services that may be of interest to You. By accessing OZEE, you expressly consent to receiving such communications from us at regular intervals.

However, if you do not wish to receive any communication from us, You may request to opt-out by writing to us at response@ozee.com. Once, We are in receipt of Your request, We will cease sending promotional messages to You.

  1. **Security and Compliance with Laws**

We strive to protect Your Personal Information against unauthorized disclosure, misuse, unlawful use, modification, loss or destruction. We take all reasonable measures and precautions, as per standard industry practises, to keep Your Personal Information confidential. We ensure compliance with all applicable laws including but not limited to Information Technology (Reasonable security practices and procedures and sensitive personal data or information) Rules, 2011.

  1. **Contact Us**

If You require any information or clarification regarding the use of your Personal Information or this Privacy Policy or if You have any grievance with respect to use of Your Personal Information, you can contact us at response@ozee.com.

  1. **International Use**

ZDCL is a company based in India. By browsing/using OZEE, YOU hereby acknowledge that ZDCL is not responsible or liable in any manner to comply with any local laws of YOUR territory except India with respect to OZEE.
